联系方式

www.linkedin.com/in/meredithcheng (LinkedIn)

热门技能

KDB

Apache Kafka

Redis

Honors-Awards

Term Dean's Honours List for all study terms (1A, 1B, 2A, 2B, 3A, 3B, 4A, 4B)

Meredith Cheng

CS @UWaterloo | Ex-intern @Citadel @Roblox @Wish 美国

个人简介

Hi, I am a fourth-year computer science student in University of Waterloo. I have several software development experiences, and also love to do side projects with friends! During my free time, I like playing the piano, cooking and singing! Feel free to have a look on my Linkedin profile and the github!

工作经历

Citadel

8个月

Software Engineer 2023 - 2023 年 4 月 (不到 1 年)

London, England, United Kingdom

Portfolio Construction Group

Software Engineer

2022年9月-2022年12月(4个月)

New York, United States

Treasury Engineering Team

- Our team focuses on cash and collateral management, funding strategies and trading execution.

Roblox

Software Engineer

2022年6月-2022年9月(4个月)

San Mateo, California, United States

Creator Cloud Infrastructure Team △#

University of Waterloo

Undergraduate Research Assistant

2021年5月-2022年8月(1年4个月)

Waterloo, Ontario, Canada

2021 Apr - Present: Supervised by Prof. Chengnian Sun, and working on the Perses Project(a Language-agnostic program reducer).

Past research experiences:

- Supervised by Prof. Raouf Boutaba, and working on the Online Algorithm

Wish

Software Engineer 2021 年 9 月 - 2021 年 12 月 (4 个月)

San Francisco Bay Area

Logistics&Marketplace(API Dev Product Catalog team) #

Participated in the development of Generic Attribute Framework for Merchant V3 API

Ontario Ministry of Children, Community and Social Services Software Developer 2020 年 9 月 - 2021 年 4 月 (8 个月)

Toronto, Ontario

- Generated interactive reports by slicing the data sets using Cognos BI in creative ways to indicate the system status.
- Refined and automated the regression testing by 100+ test cases to improve the code coverage up to 90%.
- Performed Data Analysis using SQL to report modeling system data of IBM curam to IT team, with specialists from IBM.
- Expertise in utilizing Azure DevOps and Agile to update daily changes and comminicated frequently in MS Teams.

教育经历

University of Waterloo

Computer Science, Artificial Intelligence Specialization, Minor in Pure Mathematics · (2019年9月-2023)

Georgia Institute of Technology

Master's degree, Computer Science · (2023)

Chengdu Shude High School Secondary School, General Studies